(Dan:)Wait, wait.
You're scared of Bernadette?
(Penny:)Yeah, kind of.
I thought it was just me!
E-Everyone thinks she's so nice
(Dan:)with that squeaky little voice.
(Penny:)I know, but she's
kind of a bully!
(stammers)
She is!
I-I didn't even want
to meet you,
(Dan:)but, uh, I was too scared
to say no to her.
Me, too!
Yeah, yeah!
One-one time, I had...
Oh! (laughs)
I had to tell her
(Dan:)we were cutting
the-the research funding
(Dan:)for one of the drugs
she was developing.
(Penny:)What happened?
I couldn't do it!
She's still working on it!
(laughs)
(laughing)
Oh!
(Dan:)We're not gonna tell her
about this, right?
Oh, my God, no!
No, no...
(Sheldon:)At the hot dog stand
in the Denver train station...
(Sheldon:)Heinz ketchup.
(Sheldon:)At the hot dog stand
(Sheldon:)in the Salt Lake City
train station...
(Sheldon:)Heinz ketchup.
(Sheldon:)At the hot dog stand in the
Indianapolis train station...